Chiara is already in Prague.
That's why what you're saying
is impossible.
She was at Sir Norberto's house earlier.
It has been confirmed by Carlota.
Open your eyes to the truth
that your greatest enemy here
is the person you love.
I said that's enough.
Mikoy!
You know, Chiara was right.
I really need to be careful with you.
You're doing all of this to break us up.
Because you like me.
Who are you really?!
You went to Mikoy?
You went to Mikoy and told him,
that Chiara is La Fornarina.
Our asset's security has been compromised.
So I had to warn him.
When we turn a witness we bring them here.
But what did you do?
You dumped Carlota here.
Then you went straight to Mikoy.
Didn't you hear me?
I had to warn Mikoy.
Because Viktor suspects him.
No. What you did was,
you told him that Chiara is La Fornarina.
Okay? You wasted everything
we started, Alex.
I built this case.
So if anyone's
bringing down the Moravianos,
it's me!
Do you want us
to start counting our sacrifices now?
The hardships
we've endured for this mission?
That Mikoy could already be compromised.
And if it's true that
Chiara is La Fornarina.
There's no way Mikoy doesn't know that.
There's no way he doesn't know
that the woman
he shares a bed with every day
could be the ultimate Moraviano.
And someone who could
become the future leader
of the biggest syndicate
we may never be able to bring down.
Because clearly,
you're not listening anymore.
You're blind and deaf to the truth.
If you remove me from this case,
then you're also
protecting the Moravianos.
You're the one who should stand down.
Why don't you try?!
Try to disarm me
and let's see what happens.
You're too…
- attached to Mikoy.
- What's going on here?
What's the problem?
- Sir.
- What's happening with you two?
Really?!
I just turned one Moraviano agent.
If we're counting contributions,
every breakthrough in this case
came from me.
We're here because of me.
And you have the nerve to say
that I'm hurting this mission.
Alex.
But with what you're doing now,
you're the one ruining this case.
You're prioritizing Mikoy
instead of taking down the Moravianos.
How am I compromised?!
Because you're too blind to see
that Mikoy could already
be a Moraviano now.
That's enough!
You two.
You're going to destroy this agency.
So stop it already!
Especially in front of the agents.
What happened to your teamwork?
You're arguing in front
of all these agents.
You two are so concerned in this case
that you're dragging everyone down
by demoralizing the team.
Go ahead.
You know, son.
I used to have a simple dream.
For you not to experience the hardships
I went through.
But it seems I was wrong.
I never wanted you to carry this burden.
If only I could take it back,
I wouldn't let this happen.
If I could only turn back time,
I would never let this happen.
But we can't change that anymore.
So starting now…
I'm here.
You, Angelito, and your mother
are who I will choose.
I will never leave you, son…
Mikoy.
In every battle you face.
You're like a daughter to me, Agent Alex.
So let me ask you.
Is it true that
you are losing your goddamned mind?
Agent Sianong is right.
You're becoming very unpredictable.
First, you let Carlota go.
Then, you gave information to our asset
about his girlfriend.
Information that has not been verified.
How did Mikoy react?
He wasn't happy, right?
Why did you do that?
Is it true?
That you're getting attached to him?
That you're falling for him
and starting to like him?
Don't answer that.
I don't care about your feelings.
I care about you as an agent.
I want a complete rundown
of where we are in this case.
NORBERTO S. RUIZ
GENERAL
And there's something in the oven.
Please take it out and put the dish in.
Bring it upstairs too, thank you.
Yes, I may have overdone it a little.
Viktor.
Our daughter.
I'm not used to seeing her like this.
What do we need to do?
Hey, I have a girlfriend.
Yes, I know you love Chiara.
But wake up, Son.
Mom! Mom.
Were you surprised, Son?
Wait.
Wait, why are you still sleeping
when it's already noon?
Don't you have work?
But before you answer that.
I cooked breakfast
and we're having a feast.
So get up now.
Come on.
Hurry up.
I know you're all worried.
About the consecutive attacks
from the Moravianos.
And if you think
we're just going to stand here
and take all their attacks.
Well.
It wasn't life-threatening,
but it still hurt.
That's why
she went to my house to recover.
I took care of her, sir.
I even made her rice porridge.
I also cooked her my favorite dish, adobo.
But the thing is, sir.
I had a hard time deciding
what kind of adobo to make for her.
Because there are many kinds of adobo.
There's white adobo
with vinegar with soy sauce.
There's also adobo with sauce.
But it's not debatable
whether it's paksiw or adobo.
But of course, what I made was.
He was able to provide us
actionable intelligence that will lead us
to a secret center
where they process their
illegal operations.
As hard as Pacquiao's right hook!
With all due respect, sir,
Pacquiao's left hook is the killer blow.
Do you also want to get hit
by Pacquiao's right hook?
This stays between us.
Just between us.
Because I have a secret when making adobo.
My secret is…
I add one or two drops
of 50-year-old Balsamico Di Modena.
You're making excuses.
No.
Would I really hide the truth from you?
The Viktor Valtrovi?
Already dead?
Can't you torture me first?
At least stab me in the eye, sir.
Good grief.
Just hearing your voice makes me tremble.
It's just that
there's someone scarier than you.
Sir, I could see the anger in her eyes.
You know she'll do anything
just to get rid of what she's feeling.
I'm a father too.
So I understand you.
Sir Viktor,
I also have a daughter.
And when she feels that way,
I would do everything
just to make her feel better.
This isn't our fight.
There are things that no matter what we do
we can't help Chiara with.
Only she can know what she should do.
I was surprised by your father.
I only called him to ask
how the land he was fixing was going.
Then suddenly,
I was surprised when he said
he was coming back to Manila,
so of course I followed right away.
That was the only way
to make sure I can see
my two troublemakers, right?
Now you, Mario.
You should finish dealing
with that land already.
At this rate,
it'll just end up as potted soil.
You can never tell.
Angelito, thank you so much
for joining us today.
You had time for us.
How's school going?
Oh! right.
What's the name of his girlfriend again?
Sofie!
You know, I know all those Gen Z labels.
That's right, labels.
Do you two have labels now?
Or are you just vibing?
See? I know what I'm talking about.
Do you know what?
Cebu misses you all so much!
Betchay misses you so much.
The drinking sessions miss you all
with what's-his-name again?
Who was that again? What's his name?
Oh, Dekyo.
Everyone misses you,
so when are you going on vacation?
That's what I'm saying.
Angelito.
You are not allowed to enroll
in summer classes
because I don't want you
getting stressed, Son.
Think about it.
You know the word "burnt out"?
I don't want that happening to you.
Okay? So go on a vacation.
Okay? Promise me that.
Mikoy, I just thought of something.
Why don't you bring Chiara? To Cebu!
We have so many
beautiful beaches there, right?
What's the name
of that beautiful beach again?
Bantayan Island.
I just thought of something.
Let's also bring Donabel and Viktor too!
Mikoy.
Where's Chiara?
You know, I noticed something.
I've been here for a while,
but I haven't seen her.
Where is she?
Mom, Chiara is in Prague.
She just has something
she needs to take care of.
You should've gone with her.
Wait.
You didn't go with her,
or she didn't want you to?
Oh, dear, Son. Tell me the truth.
Tell your father and me.
Are you two okay?
Are you having problems?
Tell us the truth.
Mom, we're okay.
We're getting along fine.
Chiara's just really busy.
But she'll come back.
Let's eat now.
Enough with all the talking.
You all talk too much.
I'm a father too.
So I understand you.
Sir Viktor,
I also have a daughter.
And when she feels that way,
I would do everything
just to make her feel better.
VALTROVI
There are things that no matter what we do
we can't help Chiara with.
Only she can know what she should do.
What?! Mikoy? I don't understand.
What did Mikoy do?
Copy, Mother Eagle. Let's go.